{
    "id": "22d3cf5d189741fb91dd73eeb4edb3f7",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I want to know …………………………………. you don’t talk to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "why",
                "how"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him ………………………….. he was doing on my computer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. he was taken to hospital, he could not be saved.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. Despite is not a conjunction. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Despite",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. we do not get the loan, we will have to shelve the project.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. he quits drinking, his health will not improve.",
            "description": "Unless is similar to if not.",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She told me ………………………… she was going abroad.",
            "description": "That is the conjunction most commonly used to introduce a noun clause.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked hard …………………………… he could finish the project before the deadline.",
            "description": "The conjunction so that expresses purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "such that",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She smiled …………………………… she knew everything.",
            "description": "All of these are possible here with different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "even if",
                "though",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me ………………………… I could help him.",
            "description": "Either if or whether can be used to introduce an yes/no question.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited and waited …………………………. they did not come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "as",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. he was injured, he could not play.",
            "description": "As shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… I was the only boy in a class full of girls, I felt awkward.",
            "description": "All of these words show the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Since",
                "Because",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        }
    ]
}